ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Administration Program Files. (Box 44)
  - Effective Discipline 03W038 Public 5/18-19/2004 Henderson/Rebholz (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Investigation Tools 03W039 Public 5/20 Henderson/Rebholz, 2003-2004 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - LR for Managers 03W040 Public 5/12-13/2004 Henderson/Rebholz Canceled (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Labor Matters Artist Reception 03W041 UAW Region 9 7/14/2003 Grogan, 2003-2004 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Leadership for Diverse World 03W042 CU-NYC 7/15 and 7/22/03 Henderson, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 38)
- Planning sheets, program info reports (PIR). (Box 45)
  - PIR Info From Planning Sheets, 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Assorted Activity Summaries, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Planning Sheets 7/1/95 - 6/30/96, 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Planning Sheets - 7/1/94 - 6/30/95, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Workers, Unons and the Auto Industry Local PEL+ Auto Industry in Transition Local PEL, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Planning Sheets 7/1/93-6/30/95, 1993-1995 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Western Region Programs 1994-95 Fiscal Year, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Institute Non-Credit Programs, 1987-1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Planning Sheets 7/1/96 - 6/30/97, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Planning Sheets, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Western Region PIR and Program Information PIR, 1987-1997 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Fall '87; Winter '88; Spring '88 Summer '88 CR/ Programs Report. Forms, 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - PIR Instructions, 1989-2000 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Industry Studies: Expenses + Program List/ Summary, 1986-1991 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - AIS Program Summary + Info for Program Information Report and Survey of Non-Credit Instructional Activities, 1993-1998 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Program Planning Sheets (Folder 1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Program Planning Sheets (Folder 2 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Information for Program Information Report and Survey of Non-Credit Instructional Activities (Folder 1 of 2), 1986-1995 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Information for Program Information Report and Survey of Non-Credit Instructional Activities, 1986-1992 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Administration Program Files-Credit. (Box 46)
  - 98SSSBF08303 Oral Communication 04/20/199 06/08199 Houghton College Gerald Regan Cancelled, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - 98SSSBF09702 + 03 Dynamics of Organizational Behavior 04/23/199 06/11/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Ellen Aheam, 1997- 1998 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - 98FSSBF04501 Legal Aspects of Employmnt 10/14/199 12/16/019 VA Hospital (Room 1109-C) Radhika lyer, 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - 99WLSBF25201 Contract Bargaining 01/14/199 04/01/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 474 Richard Lipsitz, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 98WSSBF03503 Employee Relations for Supervisors 01/21/98 04/08/98 Houghton College Patrick Phelan, 1993-1998 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - 98WSSBF03501 Employee Relations for Supervisors 01/20/98 04/07/98 Maryvale Schools Campus Austin Scaccia, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - 98WSSBF03504 Employee Relations for Supervisors 01/21/98 05/08/98 Cornell University ILR Ellen Aheam Cancelled, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - 98WSSBF09203 Dynamics of Interpersonal Behavior 01/21/98 04/08/98 Houghton College Patricia Brady, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - 98WSSBF09202 Dynamics of Interpersonal Behavior 01/20/98 04/07/98 Maryvale Schools Campus Jeanne Grippi, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - 98WSSBF09201 Dynamics of Interpersonal Behavior 01/20/98 04/07/98 Maryvale Schools Campus Jeanne Grippi, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - 98FLSBF01301 Urban Problems and Unions 09/17/199 12/01/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - 98FLSBF01101 Labor History 09/17/199 12/10/199 Alex Blair, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - 98WWSSBF01601 Conflict Resolution 01/20/98 04/07/98 Maryvale Schools Campus Ellen Aheam, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - 10'99 - LS Correspondence, 1991-1999 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Winter '99 PR, 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - W'99 - SS Correspond., 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - 98FSSBF08201 + 082 -02 Effective Business Writing 09/15/199 12/08/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Gerald Regan, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - 98SLSBF04401 Work Organ and Troubled Emp 04/23/199 06/04/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Linda Donahue, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - 98WSLSBF03001 Labor and the American Economy 04/23/199 06/04/199, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - 98SLSBF08401 Communications in Organizing Unions 04/23/199 06/04/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Catherine Nugent, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - 98SLSBF3002 Labor and the American Economy 04/23/199 06/11/199 UAW- Region 9 Charles Whalen, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - 1998 - BLS Graduation Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - SS '98 Graduation, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - 98FSSBF00201 Stress Management in the Workplace 09/15/199 12/08/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Robert Delprino (Folder 1 of 2), 1997- 1998 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - 98FSSBF00201 Stress Management in the Workplace 09/15/199 12/08/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Robert Delprino (Folder 2 of 2), 1997- 1998 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - 98SSSBF06801 Curr Issues in Mgmt 05/13/199 07/08/199 VA Hospital Kenneth Kumiega, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - 98FGRDBF5560A Human Resource Management 09/25/199 11/13/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Richard Morano, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - 98FGRDBF684A Employment Discrimination and the Law 09/16/199 11/18/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Joseph Giroux Jr., 1996- 1998 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - 98FLSBF25302 Contract Administration 09/17/199 12/10/199 UAW - Region 9 Robert Rohrer, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - 98FLSF08901 Labor Law II 09/17/199 12/01/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Robert Reden, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - 98FLSBF25301 Contract Administration 09/17/199 12/10/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Mark Jurenovich, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - 98FSSBF04901 Motivation and Productivity 09/15/199 12/08/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Austin Scaccia, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - 98FSSBF05301 + 053-02 Principles of Supervision 09/15/199 12/08/199 Maryvale Schools Campus Ellen Ahearn, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- Credit program registration alpha t-2. (Box 47)
  - T- Registration Forms, 1995-1998 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - U - Registration Form, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - V- Program Registration Form, 1995-1997 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - ILR Extension Division Credit Program Registration Form, 1995-1998 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - W- Program Registration Form, 1995-1998 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Y- Program Registration Form, 1998-1999 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Z- Program Registration Form, 1998-1999 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Fall Term 1993 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Spring Term II4/21/93 - 6/2/93, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Spring Term I 1/13/93 - 4/7/93, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Fall 1992 Term 9/16/92 - 12/16/92 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Spring 1992 (4/29 to 6/3) (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Spring 1992 (1/22 to 4/8/92) (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Fall 1991 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies and PEF Labor Studies Spring Term 1991 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies and PEF/PSTP Labor Studies Winter 1991 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies and PEF/PSTP Labor Studies Fall Term 1990 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies and PEF/PSTP Labor Studies Spring Term 1990 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Winter Term 1990 Buffalo Labor Studies and PEF/PSTP Labor Studies (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Fall Term 1989 Buffalo Labor Studies and PEF/PSTP Labor Studies (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Spring Term 1989 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Winter Term 1989 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Fall Term 1988 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies and PEF/PSTP Labor Studies Spring Term 1988 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Winter Term 1988 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Attendance Sheets Fall 1987 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Attendance Sheets Spring 1987 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Winter, 1987 Term (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Fall Term, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Grades of "INC" Fall 1990 and Before, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Spring, 1983 Term, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Winter, 1983 Term (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Fall, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Winter, 1984 Term Attendance Records (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Attendance Sheets Spring 1984 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Winter Term 1985 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - BLS 1984 Fall Term Attendance Records (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Spring Term 1985 Attendance/ Grades Record (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Fall 1985 Term (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Winter Term 1986 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Spring 1986 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Fall, 1979 Spet. 19th - Dec. 12th, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Spring - 1979 April 11 - May 16 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Winter, 1979 VI + VII (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Fall Term 9/27 = 12/20/78 Groups VI VII, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - Spring Term of 1978- 6 Weeks April 12 - May 17 V + VI (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - Fall, 1980 Term (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - Spring, 1980 Term April 9 - May 14 1980 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - Winter, 1980 Term January 9 - March 26, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Fall, 1982 Term (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Spring, 1982 Grades (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Winter, - 1982 (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - Fall 1981 Labor Studies Attendance Record (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Winter, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Spring, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 55)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program October - December 1974 (Box 47, Folder 56)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program March - May, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 57)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program January - March, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 58)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Fall, 1973 Term (October - December ) (Box 47, Folder 59)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program March - June, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 60)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program January - March, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 61)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program October - December, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 62)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program January - March, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 63)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program March - June, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 64)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program September - December, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 65)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Fall, 1976 Term (Box 47, Folder 66)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Winter, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 67)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Spring, 1977 Term IV +V (Box 47, Folder 68)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program Fall, 1877 Term, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 69)
  - Winter Term Jan- April 1978 (Box 47, Folder 70)
  - April - May, 1976 Groups III and IV Buffalo Labor Studies (Box 47, Folder 71)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies Program January, 1976 Term (Box 47, Folder 72)
- Administration Program Files-Credit. (Box 48)
  - PEF-Fall 1990-Contemporary Labor Issues (Flood) (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - PEF Credit Program 86W091 Public Sector Collective Bargaining (242) April 22 - July 8, 1987 Hartman (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - PEF- Public Sector Labor Law (Poch) Fall 87, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - PSTP/ PEF-LBR, Gov, Politics-Millar-Spring 88, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - PSTP/PEF Spring 1988 Term (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - PSTP/PEF Labor History (Sholes) Winter 88, 1987-1988 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - PSTP/PEF Contract Adm (Hassberg) Winter 88, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - PEF/PSTP-Spring 991 Public Sector Collective Bargaining (Suggs), 1991 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - PEF-Spring 1990-Labor Govern and Politics (Millar) (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - PSTP/PEF - Labor History - Sholes-Spring '89, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - PSTP/ PEF-Public Sector Labor Law-Poch Fall 89, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - PSTP/PEF-Winter '90-Cont.Admin. -Berkhoudt, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - PEF/PSTP - Winter Term 1991 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - PSTP/PEF Winter, 1988 Term (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - PSTP/PEF-Labor and Amer Econ-Davis-Spring 88, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - PSTP/PEF-Contemp LBR Issues-Flood-Summer 88, 1985-1988 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Replacement Certificates, 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - 1974 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - 1975 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - 1976 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - 1977 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 21)
    One photograph
  - 1978 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - 1979 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - 1980 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - 1981 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - 1982 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - 1983 Buffalo Labor Studies Graduation (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - 1986 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - 1985 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - 1986 BLS Graduation (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - BLS Graduation 1987 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - BLS Graduation 1988 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Invitations, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Speakers/Entertainment, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Programs, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Certificates, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Publicity, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - Certificate Speech + Misc. Documents, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - Program, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - Press Release, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - Invitation, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - Certificates, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - Speaker/Entertainment, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - Labor Studies Certificate Announcements, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - Accounting, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 45)
- Program Files. (Box 49)
  - BLS '06 Correspondence, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - BLS S'06 Graduation, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Principles of Leadership 06W200 Seneca Nation of Indians 6/2108/8/06 Rebholz, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Effective Oral Communication 06W201 Seneca Nation 8/15-9/26/06 Rebholz, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - 06WLB120BF01 Stress Mgmt 1/26/4/13/2006 Brown (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - 06WLB120BF01 Stress Mgmt 1/26/4/13/2006 Brown (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - 06WLS043BF01 Blair and Lipsitz Labor and Film 3/7114/11/2006 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - 06WLS220BF01 Health Benefits and Policy 1/24//4/11/2006 Zazycki (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - 06WLS220BF01 Health Benefits and Policy 1/24//4/11/2006 Zazycki (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - 05FLS255BF01 Blair 9/22-15/15/05 Maryvale Labor History, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Employment Law for Leaders 05W204 RSA Solutions 8/9/05-10/4/05 Rebholz, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Principles of Leadership/Supervision 05W205 Tops Markets Inc. 8/23/05 - 11/2/05 Rebholz, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Winter 2006 PSA/PR, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - W06 Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - 06WLS008BF01 Psy of Communications 1/24//2/28/2006 Regan (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Dynamic Presentation Skills for Leaders 05W207 RSA Solutions 10/11/05-12/6/05 Rebholz, 2005-2006 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - 05LS259BF01 Union Organizing 9/15-12/6/05 Maryvale, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Effective Business Writing for Leaders 05W227 RSA/ FISERV Lending Solutions 5/17 7/19/05 Rebholz, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - The Voice of Labor: It's All For The Kids "Telethon 2005" (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - 05FLS253BF01 Jurenovich 9/22-12/15/05 Maryvale Contract Administration, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Fall Insurance + Program Listings, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Dynamics of Organizational Behavior 05W203 Seneca Nation of Indians 7/28/05-9/15/05 Rebholz, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - 05FLS061BF01 Grande 11/1-12/6/05 BFLO Workforce Dev PERS Computers Cancelled, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Administration Program Files-Credit. (Box 50)
  - Labor and Film 00SLSBF04301 Richard Lipsitz 04/20/200 06/01/200 Maryvale Community Education Bldg., Room 209 Canceled (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Labor and the American Economy 00SLSBF03001 Charles Whalen 04/20/200 06/01/200 Maryvale Community Education Bldg., Room 104 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Labor and the American Economy 00SLSBF03002 Charles Whalen/Stout 04/20/200 06/01/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 479 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - 500 SS Grad Comm, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Work Organizations and Troubled 00SSSBF04401 Robert Delprino 04/11/200 06/06/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 483 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Effective Oral Communications 00SSSBF08301 Gerald Regan 04/11/200 06/06/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 481 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Teambuilding in Groups 00SSSBF27701 Lisa Black-Hawkins 04/15/200 06/03/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 460 Cancelled (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Dynamics of Organizational 00SSSBF09702 Ellen Ahearn 04/11/200 06/06/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 479 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration II 00SADRBF022A James Meloon 04/13/200 06/08/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 460 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Negotiating and Settlement 00SADRBF046A Dennis Campagna 04/11/200 06/06/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 460 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Work Organization and Troubled 00SLSBF04401 Charles Cannon 04/20/200 06/01/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 481 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - 00WSSBF24601 Business and Professional Speaking 01/18/200 04/04/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 483 Gerald Regan (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - 00WSSBF03501 00WSSBF03502 Employee Relations for Supervisors 01/18/200 04/04/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 481 Austin Scaccia (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - BLS (2000) Graduation, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - 00WADRBF040A Mediation II 01/20/200 04/06/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 460 Krista Gottlieb (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - 00WADRBF020A Arbitration I 01/20/200 04/06/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 460 James Meloon (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - 00WSSBF09201 00WSSBF090202 Dynamics of Interpersonal Behavior 01/18/200 04/04/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 479 Patricia Brady (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - 00WLSBF05001 Privacy Issues in the Workplace 01/13/200 03/30/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 479 Catherine Creighton (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - 00WLSBF01401 Labor Law I: Private Sector 01/13/200 03/20/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 481 William Grande, 1999- 2000 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - 00WLSBF07701 Bargaining Health Care Benefits 01/13/200 03/30/200 Maryvale Schools Campus. Classroom 483 Frederick Zazycki (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - 00WLSBF25201 Contract Bargaining 01/13/200 03/30/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 479 Richard Lipsitz, 1998-2000 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - 00WLSBF04201 Labor Law I: Public Sector 01/13/200 03/30/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 472 Joel Poch (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - 00WLSBF07401 Science. Technology and Labor 01/13/200 03/30/200 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 481 Alan Stout Cancelled (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - 00WLSBF09001 Workers' Compensation and Disability 01/13/200 03/30/200 Maryvale Community Education Bldg., Room 20 Lindy Korn Cancelled (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - 00WLSBF08901 Labor Law II 01/13/200 03/30/200 Maryvale Community Education Bldg., Room 104 Christine Kroetsch Cancelled (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - 99FADRBF039A Mediation I 09/23/199 12/16/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 460, 1995-1999 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - 99FADRBF016A Conflict Resolution 09/23/199 12/16/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 460 Charlene Brumley, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - 00FADRBF016A Dynamics of Human Conflict 09/28/2000 11/16/2000 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom Timothy Mordaunt (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - 99FLBF06901 Survey in Worker Particip 09/18/199 10/09/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 460 Susan Woods, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - 99FLSBF07601 Occup Safety and Hlth Admin 09/09/199 12/09/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 483 Nellie Brown, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - 99FLSBF01101 99FLSBF01102 Labor History 09/09/199 12/09/199 Maryvale Community Education Bldg., Room Alex Blair, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - 99FLSBF25301 Contract Administration 09/09/199 12/09/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 479 Mark Jurenovich, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - 99FLSBF08901 Labor Law II 09/09/199 12/09/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 483 Robert Reden, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - 99FLSBF00802 Psy of Comm: Listening 09/09/199 12/09/199 Maryvale Community Education Bldg., Room Gerald Regan, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - 99FLSBF00101 99FLSBF00102 Personal Computers as a Union Tool 09/09/199 12/09/199 Maryvale Schools Campus-Computer Lab Rm William Grande, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - 99FSSBF05301 99FSSBF05302 Prin of Supv: Eff Mgmt Str 09/21/199 12/14/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 479 Ellen Ahearn, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - 99FSSBF99901 Creative Problem Solving 09/21/199 12/14/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 472 Austin Scaccia, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Creative Problem Solving Readings, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - 99FSSBF08201 99FSSBF08202 Written Communication 09/21/199 12/14/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 481Gerald Regan, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - ILR: Buffalo Labor Studies + Alternative Dispute Resolution Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - F'99 BLS Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - F'99 SS Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - F'99 ADR Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - Fall '99 Press Releases, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - 99SLSBF03001 Labor and The American Economy 04/22/199 06/03/199 Maryvale Schools Campus, Classroom 474 Susan Davis, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - 99SLSBF08401 Communications in Organizing Unions 04/15/199 05/27/199 UAW-Region 9 Marc Panepinto, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 46)
- Program Files-H&S. (Box 51)
  - CHIP Prog # 1340 Date 04/16/96 Client: Cornell WR Title: EEO+S+H, 1990-1996 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Some documents very curled on one side + One transparency
  - CHIP Prog # 1341 Date 01/30/96 Client: ALCOSH Cuba Schools Title: Cancer IAQ, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - CHIP Prog # Date: Client: Cornell-WR Title: SEC'Y'S Day, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Work Safe! Work Smart! Breakfast Seminar for Office Professionals, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - CHIP Prog # 1345 Date: 04/18/96 Client: Madigan Engineers Title: FAQ, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - CHIP Prog # 1346 Date: 01/29/96 Client: F. Dolce, ESQ Title: Mnl Welding (Folder 1 of 2), 1990-1996 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - CHIP Prog # 1346 Date: 01/29/96 Client: F. Dolce, ESQ Title: Mnl Welding (Folder 2 of 2), 1996 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - CHIP Prog # 1347 Date: 05/06/96 Client: Cornell Univ.-WR Title: S+ H for Supervisors, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - CHIP Prog # 1348 Date Client Title, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - CHIP Prog # 1352 Date: 03/06/96 Client: Trek, Inc. Title: Hazcom, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - CHIP Prog # 1365 Date: 07/03/96 Client: M. Reilly, ESQ. Title: In RE: J. France, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - CHIP Prog # 1370, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - CHIP Prog # 1373 Date: 12/06/96 Client: ALCOSH Title: IAQ, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - S+ H Series s- Health Hazards of Chemicals Prog # 1374 08/08/96 Client: Cornell ILR, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - 1261, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - CHIP Prog # 1262 date: 09/29/95 client: Albany BOCES title: IAQ, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Client: ALCOSH/Falconer Cent. School NYSUT - Chemical Hazard, 1995-1996 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - CHIP Prog # 1265 date: 07/14/95 client: Jim Austin title: IAQ, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - CHIP Prog # 1266 date: 11/14/95 client: Boehringer-Mannhem Corp. title: IAQ, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 19)